David Santer

Web Developer E-mail davidsanter397@gmail.com

Summary

Bringing more than 9 years of experience leading website design projects, including gathering user requirements, producing code, creating mockups and enhancing designs. Focused on creating clean, robust code with exceptional security. Achieves compatibility targets while meeting and exceeding customer demands.

Skill Highlights

- Website optimization
- Software Best Practices
- Web development projects

- Agile workflow
- Interpersonal Communication
- Dependable and Responsible

Experience

Full Stack Developer - 01/2017 to current New York, NY

- Developed and executed 200+ test procedures for software components
- Analyzed systems flow, data usage, and work processes; investigated 100% of problem areas
- Presented and conveyed ideas and designs with 4+ technical teams and 12+ business partners.
- Developed 40+ applications following Agile product development methodologies.
- Integrated existing software into 13 upgraded, modified systems for higher performance
- Communicated with line of business and managed the overall status and health of 20+ applications.

Front End Developer - 01/2014 to 12/2016 New York, NY

- Developed a node.js server to validate membership and track digital badges being used, saving the company \$22.5K.
- Rebuilt 4-year-old SaaS application in React 15 and Redux with full user experience redesign to release a beta MVP in 8 months.
- Reduced average valuation review time by 46%, and saved service providers an average of 84% due to click-fee reductions.
- Created non-technical descriptions of operations and workflow to enable non-coding team to function with minimal interruption.
- Integrated an automated property valuation model fed by machine learning Python data.

Education

University of Dalware – Master of Science, Computer Science 2008-2012

Certifications

Programming Languages: JavaScript, HTML5, CSS, SQL, MySQL.

References

https://github.com/davidsanter397/